Guide to the Fred Chappell Papers, 1944-2019 and undated RL.00213
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Fred Chappell papers
1944-2019 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Chappell, Fred, 1936-
RL.00213
158 Linear Feet
5.9 Gigabytes
Access Restrictions
Electronic records in this series have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
Provenance
The Fred Chappell Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift and purchase from 1964-2018.
Biographical Note
Fred Chappell Chronology
1936, May 28 Born in Canton, N.C., to James Taylor and Anne (Davis) Taylor
1959, Aug. 2 Married Susan Nicholls
1960 Birth of son, Heath
1961 B.A., Duke University
1964 M.A., Duke University
1964- Member of English Department Faculty, University of North Carolina at Greensboro
1966 Rockefeller Foundation Grant
1968 National Institute and American Academy award in literature
1971 Prix de Meilleur des Lettres Etrangers, Académie Française, for Dagon
1972 Roanoke-Chowan Poetry Cup for The World Between the Eyes
1973 Sir Walter Raleigh Award for The Gaudy Place
1978 Roanoke-Chowan Poetry Cup for River: A Poem
1979 Roanoke-Chowan Poetry Cup for Bloodfire: A Poem
1980 North Carolina Award in Literature
1985 Bollingen Prize in Poetry, Yale University Library
1988 Named Excellence Foundation Professor, Burlington Industries Professorship at UNC-G
1993 T.S. Eliot Award, Ingersoll Prizes in Literature and the Humanities
1997-2002 Poet Laureate of North Carolina
2000 SEBA (Southeast Booksellers Association) Book Award, Fiction
2010 John Tyler Caldwell Award for the Humanities, North Carolina Humanities Council
Fred Davis Chappell (1936- ) is an author and poet. He was an English professor for 40 years at the University of North Carolina at Greensboro. He was the Poet Laureate of North Carolina from 1997–2002. He attended Duke University
Collection Overview
The fully processed portion of the Fred Chappell Papers spans the dates 1960-1997, with the bulk being dated after 1970. There are several additions covering the years 1998 through 2015. The collection consists of correspondence; writings by Chappell and other authors; printed material (primarily serials containing stories, poems, and articles by Chappell but also clippings); legal and financial papers; speeches and addresses; interviews; and other material. Documents relate to Chappell's personal life and career, both as a student and writer at Duke University, where he studied under well-known creative writing teacher William Blackburn, and as a writer and professor at the University of North Carolina at Greensboro (UNC-G). The collection documents the entire length and breadth of Chappell's multifaceted career, beginning with the years just after he completed his undergraduate studies at Duke and started his first novel at the urging of Hiram Haydn, an editor to whom Blackburn had introduced him. Letters, manuscripts, and notebooks provide insight into Chappell's developing literary career, his academic activities at UNC-G, and his growing involvement with a large network of writers, including a number of his former students. Many prominent American authors, especially Southern ones, are represented in the collection. Among the most frequent correspondents are Kelly Cherry, Grace DiSanto, George Garrett, Marianne Gingher, Dana Gioia, Donald Hall, Heather Ross Miller, Robert Morgan, Eve Shelnutt, and Dabney Stuart. Notebooks, manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, and printed material document the development of Chappell's career across all the genres in which he writes. Supporting material in non-print media, including photographs and audio and video cassettes of readings, document public aspects of his career.
The Correspondence Series, arranged chronologically in Incoming and Outgoing subseries, discloses the range of Chappell's interests and activities in the literary community. The letters not only provide a portrait of his development as a poet and novelist but also demonstrate his active roles in supporting the careers of other writers and promoting the literary community. These latter activities are documented by his numerous affirmative responses to a broad range of requests to read drafts of works-in-progress, write recommendations for other writers for grants and awards, write reviews and provide blurbs for new publications, serve as the judge of contests, speak at conferences and workshops, and serve in various advisory and editorial capacities for literary journals. The correspondence also provides much information about his teaching career and his legacy of students who develop successful careers of their own, such as Cherry, Miller, Morgan, and Shelnutt. The bulk of the outgoing correspondence dates to 1990 or after, when, at the request of the Rare Book, Manuscript, and Special Collections Library, Chappell began retaining copies of all outgoing correspondence.
The Writings by Chappell Series is divided into subseries by genres with the exception of one subseries based on format, the Notebooks Subseries. Since Chappell writes with relatively few hand corrections on any particular stage of his work, the development of an individual work is often apparent only by comparing various complete drafts in manuscripts, typescripts, and proofs. The notebooks are particularly valuable in this regard, providing what often appear to be the earliest versions of works. The notebooks also indicate the facility with which Chappell moves from one genre to another, as most of them are not devoted to a single work or genre but rather include poems, stories, novel fragments, essays, reviews, translations, and drafts of correspondence following one after the other. This versatility is further reflected by the Printed Materials Series, which contains extensive serials with Chappell's publications in multiple genres, especially fiction, poetry, and reviews. At the end of this series, the Clippings Subseries documents his public and critical reception with copies of reviews and essays about his work and publicity about it.
The Miscellaneous Series contains a variety of flyers, leaflets, newsletters, and examples of fan mail that further demonstrate his literary career. Prominent here are such items as the proofs for a 1990 symposium about his poetry and newsletters of the Fellowship of Southern Writers. It also contains two small subseries of audio and video cassettes of readings, interviews, and work by other authors.
The Writings by Others Series contains manuscripts from well-known contemporary writers, ex-students, and aspiring writers seeking advice. Chappell's reactions to the manuscripts are written on many of them, often as the first draft of a letter or requested recommendation. Most writers are represented by only one or two items, but Cherry and Shelnutt are both represented by more than a dozen pieces that, together with their frequent correspondence, outline the development of their respective careers.
Later additions to the collection include incoming and outgoing correspondence, drafts and writings of Chappell's poetry, honors and awards, and printed materials and publications featuring Chappell or his work. Most accessions include bound volumes as well as writings and manuscripts by other authors or poets. There are also some oversize materials, audiovisual materials, clippings, and photographs. These additions have been loosely sorted but have not been incorporated physically or intellectually into the originally processed collection. Please consult Research Services with questions about using these materials.
Conditions Governing Access
Original audiovisual materials are closed to use. Contact Research Services in advance to request the production of viewing or use copies.
Compact discs; Black-and-white photographs; Color photographs; Audiocassettes; College teachers as authors; Creative writing (Higher education); Videocassettes; American literature -- 20th century; American poetry -- North Carolina; Authors, American -- 20th century -- Correspondence; Authors and publishers; Gioia, Dana; Hall, Donald, 1928-; Gingher, Marianne; Morgan, Robert, 1944-; Shelnutt, Eve, 1943-; Haydn, Hiram Collins, 1907-1973; Miller, Heather Ross, 1939-; Stuart, Dabney, 1937-; University of North Carolina at Greensboro -- Faculty; Garrett, George, 1929-2008; Blackburn, William, 1899-1972; Chappell, Fred, 1936-; Fellowship of Southern Writers; Duke University. Department of English -- History; DiSanto, Grace; Cherry, Kelly
- Correspondence Series, 1960-1997 and undated
  Scope and Contents note
  Arranged in Incoming Correspondence and Outgoing Correspondence subseries.
  - Incoming Correspondence Subseries, 1960-1997 and undated
    Includes letters from friends, family members, writers, teachers, students, editors, publishers, and readers of Chappell's works. Letters are arranged chronologically with undated letters at the end. Some letters include short writings as attachments. Longer writings such as drafts of entire books, complete issues of serials, and so on appear in the Writings by Others Series. Chappell frequently uses the backs of letters, envelopes, or attachments to write drafts of various material: responses to the letter at hand, poems, story fragments, translations, and autobiographical statements. A chronological list of these items appears following the box list for this subseries.
    - 1960 Nov.-1970 Jun., 21 folders (Box CI-1)
    - 1970 Jul.-1975 Apr., 17 folders (Box CI-2)
    - 1975 May-1979 Oct., 17 folders (Box CI-3)
    - 1979 Nov.-1982 Apr., 17 folders (Box CI-4)
    - 1982 May-1984 Jun., 16 folders (Box CI-5)
    - 1984 Jul.-1985 Oct., 19 folders (Box CI-6)
    - 1985 Dec.-1986 Nov., 18 folders (Box CI-7)
    - 1986 Dec.-1987 Dec., 17 folders (Box CI-8)
    - 1988 Jan.-1989 Apr., 17 folders (Box CI-9)
    - 1989 May-1990 Feb., 16 folders (Box CI-10)
    - 1990 Mar.-1990 Dec., 18 folders (Box CI-11)
    - 1991 Jan.-1991 Sept., 18 folders (Box CI-12)
    - 1991 Oct.-1992 Jun., 16 folders (Box CI-13)
    - 1992 Jul.-1993 Aug., 16 folders (Box CI-14)
    - 1993 Sept.-1994 May, 19 folders (Box CI-15)
    - 1994 Jun.-1995 Feb., 17 folders (Box CI-16)
    - 1995 Mar.-1995 Oct., 18 folders (Box CI-17)
    - 1995 Nov.-1996 Jul. 18, 17 folders (Box CI-18)
    - 1996 Jul. 19.-1997 Jan., 17 folders (Box CI-19)
    - 1997 Feb.-1997 Jun. and undated, 16 folders (Box CI-20)
    - List of Incoming Correspondence Containing Chappell Writings
      - 1964 Jul. 7: Harriet Doar; story on back, "Band of Brothers" (Box CI-1)
      - 1964 Aug. 24: Charlotte Kohler, Virginia Quarterly Review; poems attached, Hymn and Hir, The Survivors, and Renting (Box CI-1)
      - 1966 Mar. 28: George Lynn; poem attached, "Hangover Thursday" (Box CI-1)
      - 1967 Aug. 28: Paul Carroll; poems attached, rejected for anthology of young American poets (Box CI-1)
      - 1968 Jul. 22: Andrew Lytle, Sewanee Review; poem attached, The Farm (Box CI-1)
      - 1969 Nov. 3: T.J., Aim; several poems attached (Box CI-1)
      - 1971 Dec. 13: George Lynn; poem stanza on envelope (Box CI-2)
      - 1974 Sep. 26: LSU Press; changes in plan of The River (Box CI-2)
      - 1976 Jun. 18: George Core; statement on "regionalism" (Box CI-3)
      - 1978 Mar. 20: Brian Swann; translations of Italian poems (Box CI-3)
      - 1986 Jan. 14: Peter [?] of Tar River Poetry; attached poems with Chappell's revisions of Two Visions of the Magic Mirror (Box CI-7)
      - 1986 Mar. 13: Stephen Corey; notes re: poem A Prologue to the Georgics (Box CI-7)
      - 1987 Aug. 18: Joanne Wyckoff; blurb for Elizabeth Socolow's Laughing At Gravity (Box CI-8)
      - 1988 Feb. 21: Warren Moore; blurb for Moore's untitled book (Box CI-9)
      - 1988 Jul. 19: Michael Skube; drafts of poem, Liberal (Box CI-9)
      - 1988 Aug. 27: Mark Raney; poem Campaign Speech written on envelope (Box CI-9)
      - 1989 Nov. 20: Jane Hill; blurb for Warren Leamon's book, Unheard Melodies (Box CI-10)
      - 1989 Dec. 16: Resa Crane-Rodger; poem about "ghost love" on envelope (Box CI-10)
      - 1989 Dec. 28: Walter Bode; blurb for Chilton Williamson's The Homestead (Box CI-10)
      - 1990 Feb. 5: Gaylord Dold; blurb for William Peden's Fragments and Fictions (Box CI-10)
      - 1990 Mar. 26: Marita Garin; handwritten draft of autobiographical statement (Box CI-10)
      - 1990 Mar. 31: William Stevens; verse on envelope (Box CI-11)
      - 1990 Nov. 9: LSU Press; blurb for Kelly Cherry's The Exiled Heart (Box CI-11)
      - 1991 Feb. 13: Claire Watchel; blurb for Karen Osborne's Patchwork (Box CI-12)
      - 1991 Feb. 19: Loni Jakiela; reply about poets taking NEA or public money and the obligations thereof (Box CI-12)
      - 1991 Jul. 26: Ethan Ellenberg; blurb for Clay Reynold's book, Franklin's Crossing (Box CI-12)
      - 1991 Oct. 23: Catherine Landry; annotated publication history of poems in C (Box CI-13)
      - 1991 Nov. 25: Michael Bujega; drafts of limericks (Box CI-13)
      - 1993 Nov. 23; Stephen Corey; revisions of essay Let Me Count the Ways -- Five Love Poets (Box CI-15)
      - 1994 Feb. 12: Annie Finch, Poems and Poetics; translations of poems, Thomas More and Charles d'Orleans (Box CI-15)
      - 1994 Apr. 27: Styron Harris; poetical toast to Jack Higgs, on envelope (Box CI-15)
      - 1994 Jul. 5: Wilkie Conner; The Kiss -- Fifty Years Late by F. C. and Wilkie Conner (Box CI-16)
      - 1994 Sep. 14: Margaret Britton Vaughn; blurb for Vaughn's Kim (Box CI-16)
      - 1994 Dec. 22: David Slavitt; poem about and for Slavitt (Box CI-16)
      - 1995 May 20: Martin L. Hester; blurb for Hester's With Crockett at the Alamo (Box CI-17)
      - 1995 Aug. 7: James Applewhite; lines on back of envelope (Box CI-17)
      - 1995 Nov. 13: Robert (Bob) Sterling Gingher; draft of recommendation for Gingher on back of envelope (Box CI-18)
      - 1995 Dec. 13: Doug McCarty; draft of recommendation for McCarty on back of envelope (Box CI-18)
      - 1996 Feb. 4: Thomas Payton; blurb for Judson Mitcham's The Sweet Everlasting (Box CI-18)
      - 1996 Mar. 11: Elizabeth Tallent; recommendation for April Heck (Box CI-18)
      - 1996 Apr. 30: Stanley Lindberg; response in form of a poem on back of envelope (Box CI-18)
      - n. d.: Stephen Heller; analysis of Stephen Heller's work on back of Heller's project proposal (Box CI-20)
    - Grace DiSanto Correspondence Sub-subseries, 1978-1993 and undated
      A former student of Chappell's, DiSanto carried on a voluminous correspondence with Chappell, especially in the late 1970s, frequently attaching many pages of new poems to the letters. The decision to organize her works in a separate subseries was based on the volume of her letters and writings.
      - 1974 May-1977 Dec., 17 folders (Box CD-1)
      - 1978 Jan.-1993 Jul., 11 folders (Box CD-2)
  - Outgoing Correspondence Subseries, 1964-1997 and undated
    Includes letters to friends, family members, writers, teachers, students, editors, publishers, and readers of Chappell's works. Letters are arranged chronologically with undated letters at the end. The bulk of this series dates after 1990 when, at the Library's request, Chappell began retaining copies of all his outgoing correspondence. Drafts of outgoing correspondence also appear in the Writings by Chappell Series, Notebooks Subseries.
    - 1964 Mar.-1993 Dec., 23 folders (Box CO-1)
    - 1994 Jan.-1996 Dec., 36 folders (Box CO-2)
    - 1997 Jan.-1997 Jun., 7 folders (Box CO-3)
- Legal and Financial Papers Series, 1962-1997 and undated
  Arranged in chronological order. Includes royalty statements, tax information, contracts, etc.
  - 1962 Sept. - 1997 May and undated, 8 folders (Box LF-1)
- Writings by Chappell Series, 1960-1997 and undated
  Divided into the following genre subseries: Fiction, Poetry, Essays, Reviews, Speeches and Addresses, and Miscellaneous. Additionally, one subseries based on format, Notebooks, should be consulted to ensure seeing all versions of an item in any genre. Each subseries is alphabetized by title, with multiple drafts of individual works arranged, to the extent it can be determined, in order of composition. With all of Chappell's writings it should be noted that he seldom dates his work, so often the only clues to the date of composition are the date of publication and the date the Library received a particular accession. This latter is noted in brackets on many items as [Rec'd date]. The date in boldface after the titles of books is the original publication date.
  - Fiction Subseries, 1963-1996 and undated
    Arranged alphabetically by title, books first followed by individual stories. Versions of collected stories may appear under their own title or that of the collection. Individual stories are grouped with the collection if the Library received them that way or if page renumbering clearly indicates that a manuscript was part of a larger organization. Additional versions may appear in the Notebooks Subseries.
    - Brighten the Corner Where You Are (1989), 6 items in 10 folders (Box WF-1)
      - miscellaneous manuscripts, undated, rec'd 1986 June (Box WF-1)
      - miscellaneous typescripts, undated, rec'd 1989 June (Box WF-1)
      - typescript, 1988 Dec. 23 (Box WF-1)
      - photocopy of author-corrected typescript, undated, rec'd 1989 June (Box WF-1)
      - typescript, ca. 1988 Dec. (Box WF-1)
      - dead manuscript, 1989 Oct. 25 (Box WF-1)
    - Dagon (1968) See also Oversize Material, 8 folders
      - notebook, undated (Box WF-1)
      - notebook, undated (Box WF-1)
      - manuscript fragments, undated (Box WF-1)
      - first complete draft, undated (Box WF-1)
      - typescript, undated, rec'd 1970 Apr. (Box WF-1)
      - typescript, 1968 (Box WF-1)
      - dead manuscript, 1968 (Box WF-1)
      - digital files for Boson Books electronic edition, 1995 (Box WF-1)
    - Farewell, I'm Bound to Leave You (1996), 2 items in 3 folders
      - miscellaneous typescripts and manuscripts, undated (Box WF-1)
      - photocopy of fair typescript, undated (Box WF-1)
    - Farewell, I'm Bound to Leave You (1996), 1 item in 2 folders (Box WF-2)
      - dead manuscript, 1996 Dec. 31 (Box WF-2)
    - The Fred Chappell Reader (1990), 1 folder
      - miscellaneous notes, undated (Box WF-2)
    - The Gaudy Place (1973) See also Oversize Material, 4 items in 5 folders
      - miscellaneous manuscripts, ca. 1970 Apr., 1971 (Box WF-2)
      - typescript, 1973 Apr. 19 (Box WF-2)
      - partial typescript, ca. 1971? (Box WF-2)
      - dead manuscript, ca. 1972 (Box WF-2)
    - I Am One of You Forever (1985), 3 items in 4 folders
      - miscellaneous typescripts, undated, rec'd 1986 June (Box WF-2)
      - dead manuscript, 1985 (Box WF-2)
      - miscellaneous proofs, ca. 1985 (Box WF-2)
    - The Inkling (1965) See also Oversize Material, 5 items in 7 folders
      - 3 notebooks, undated (Box WF-2)
      - typescript, number 2 copy, undated (Box WF-2)
      - carbon copy, undated (Box WF-2)
      - bound proof, 1965 (Box WF-2)
      - miscellaneous typescript chapters and plot summary (Masterplots article), undated (Box WF-2)
    - It Is Time, Lord (1963) See also Oversize Material, 2 folders
      - notebook, undated (Box WF-2)
      - manuscript pages, undated (Box WF-2)
    - It Is Time, Lord (1963), 3 items in 5 folders (Box WF-3)
      - typescript, 1963 (Box WF-3)
      - carbon copy, undated (Box WF-3)
      - author's proof fragment, 1963 Mar. (Box WF-3)
    - Moments of Light (1980) See also Oversize Material, 1 folder
      - page proofs, 1980 Sep. 11 (Box WF-3)
    - More Shapes Than One (1991), 4 items in 7 folders
      - typescript (as Waltzes Noble and Sentimental), undated, rec'd 1991 July (Box WF-3)
      - typescript with author's corrections, undated, rec'd 1991 July (Box WF-3)
      - miscellaneous typescripts, undated, rec'd 1991 July (Box WF-3)
      - dead manuscript, 1992 Feb. 20 (Box WF-3)
    - Pete and Shirley: The Great Tarheel Novel (1995), 1 folder
      - corrected typescript, 1995 Nov. 1 (Box WF-3)
    - The Thousand Ways (unpublished, ca. 1960-1969), 5 folders
      - typescripts, manuscripts, notebooks, ca. 1960-1969, 4 folders (Box WF-3)
      - typescript, 1967 Dec. 8 (Box WF-3)
    - Untitled Novel (unpublished, ca. 1960-1969), 2 folders (Box WF-4)
      - carbon, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WF-4)
      - notebook, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WF-4)
    - Individual stories, in alphabetical order:
      - The Admirer, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - After Revelation, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Alphabet, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Aubade, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Astolpho Recalls, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - After Revelation, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - The Bad Luck, undated (Box WF-4)
      - Band of Brothers, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Barcarole, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Basic Training, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - The Beard, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Blood Shadow, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Blue Dive, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - A Broken Beginning, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Broken Blossoms, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Crow Knows, undated, rec'd 1991 July (Box WF-4)
      - Dangers of the First Floor, undated, rec'd 1970 Jan. (Box WF-4)
      - A Day in the Life, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Detour on 51, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - The Devil-Possum, 1987 May 26 (Box WF-4)
      - The Dreaming Orchid, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Duet, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. and 1990 July (2 items) (Box WF-4)
      - Elmer and Buford, ca. 1960-1969 and rec'd 1985 Oct. (2 items) (Box WF-4)
      - Going Downhill, section of unidentified novel or collection, undated, rec'd 1995 June (Box WF-4)
      - The Good Things, undated, rec'd 1970 Jan. (Box WF-4)
      - The Good Time, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Haydn Takes a Peek, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Homage to Plato, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WF-4)
      - Indiscretions, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Inheritance, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Invasions, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Judas, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Linnaeus Forgets, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - The Lodger, undated, rec'd 1993 July (Box WF-4)
      - Man Twice Married to Fire, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - The Memorial Poem, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - The Mentor, 1990 Dec. 31 (Box WF-4)
      - Miss Prue, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Mr. Bones, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Morning Star, undated, rec'd 1986 June (Box WF-4)
      - The Mountains, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - The Ninety-Ninth Foxfire Book, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Notes Toward a Theory of Flight, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - O, Suprême Clairon, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Old Times, New Times, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WF-4)
      - The Overspill, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - A Penance on Ember Mountain, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Poets, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - The Posse, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Prodigious Words, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - A Property of Hope, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - The Snow That Is Nothing in the Triangle, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - The Story Teller, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)
      - Thatch Retaliates, undated, rec'd 1985 Oct. (Box WF-4)